{
    "subject": "resource/Johnt\u00e1_Austin",
    "predicate": "ontology/hometown",
    "object": "resource/United_States",
    "human_readable": "Johnt\u00e1 Austin's hometown is United States.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9596983194351196,
            "question": "Where is Johnt\u00e1 Austin's hometown?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9380035400390625,
            "question": "Is Johnt\u00e1 Austin from the United States?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9035888314247131,
            "question": "What country is Johnt\u00e1 Austin's hometown in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8286065459251404,
            "question": "Could Johnt\u00e1 Austin be considered a citizen of the United States?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6783771514892578,
            "question": "How has Johnt\u00e1 Austin's hometown influenced their life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6338216662406921,
            "question": "Are there any famous people from the United States who share a similar background with Johnt\u00e1 Austin?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6257295608520508,
            "question": "Do you know anything else about Johnt\u00e1 Austin besides their hometown?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6161150336265564,
            "question": "Where was Johnt\u00e1 Austin raised?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5360156297683716,
            "question": "What might Johnt\u00e1 Austin's life experiences be like living in the United States?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.05478604510426521,
            "question": "What are some common characteristics of people from the United States?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Johnt\u00e1 Austin's hometown is United States.",
            "html": "dbpedia_9078_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What might Johnt\u00e1 Austin's life experiences be like living in the United States?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9078_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where was Johnt\u00e1 Austin raised?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9078_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Do you know anything else about Johnt\u00e1 Austin besides their hometown?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9078_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9078_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9078_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9078_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9078_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9078_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9078_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9078_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9078_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9078_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9078_59.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\n**Explanation:** The documents indicate that Johnta Austin is from Atlanta, Georgia, which is in the United States. Therefore, it can be inferred that his hometown is the United States."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}